
export const quizQuestions_7 = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What is the primary purpose of the React library in JavaScript?',
      choices: ['To manage server-side logic', 'To create interactive user interfaces in the browser', 'To perform data validation', 'To handle server-side rendering'],
      correctAnswer: 'To create interactive user interfaces in the browser',
    },
    {
      question: 'In JavaScript, what is the purpose of the const keyword when declaring a variable?',
      choices: ['To indicate that the variable cannot be reassigned', 'To declare a constant function', 'To specify the constant value of the variable', 'To create a variable with constant scope'],
      correctAnswer: 'To indicate that the variable cannot be reassigned',
    },
    {
      question: 'How do you define a function in JavaScript?',
      choices: ['function myFunction() { }', 'const myFunction = () => { }', 'MyFunction() { }', 'define myFunction() { }'],
      correctAnswer: 'function myFunction() { }',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the purpose of the return statement in a JavaScript function?',
      choices: ['To terminate the function execution immediately', 'To specify the return type of the function', 'To provide the output or result of the function', 'To declare a variable within the function'],
      correctAnswer: 'To provide the output or result of the function',
    },
    {
      question: 'How do you declare a variable in JavaScript using the let keyword?',
      choices: ['let myVar;', 'myVar = let;', 'declare myVar;', 'const myVar = let;'],
      correctAnswer: 'let myVar;',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the purpose of the JavaScript class keyword?',
      choices: ['To define a class of HTML elements', 'To create a new instance of an object', 'To declare a function', 'To define a blueprint for creating objects'],
      correctAnswer: 'To define a blueprint for creating objects',
    },
    {
      question: 'In JavaScript, what does the term "hoisting" refer to?',
      choices: ['The process of lifting heavy objects in the gym', 'The automatic moving of variable and function declarations to the top of their containing scope', 'The conversion of data types', 'The process of optimizing code for performance'],
      correctAnswer: 'The automatic moving of variable and function declarations to the top of their containing scope',
    },
    {
      question: 'How do you comment out a single line of code in JavaScript?',
      choices: ['<!-- This is a comment -->', '// This is a comment', '/ This is a comment /', '* This is a comment *'],
      correctAnswer: '// This is a comment',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the purpose of the JavaScript !== operator?',
      choices: ['To check if two values are not equal in value and type', 'To check if two values are equal in value and type', 'To perform a bitwise NOT operation', 'To compare the size of two numbers'],
      correctAnswer: 'To check if two values are not equal in value and type',
    },
    {
      question: 'How can you concatenate two strings in JavaScript?',
      choices: ['str1 + str2', 'str1 . str2', 'concat(str1, str2)', 'combine(str1, str2)'],
      correctAnswer: 'str1 + str2',
    }
  ],
}